velocitypayment.com 2010-06-06

# Privacy Policy | VELOCITY PAYMENT SYSTEM

## Privacy Policy

### Collection of Information

Govolution collects personal information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by visitors to our corporate website. This information is used to fulfill requests for services.

### User Tracking

The Govolution corporate website may use cookie and tracking technology. Cookie and tracking technology is useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the website, and understanding how visitors use the website. Cookies can also help customize the website for visitors.

### Data Security

Govolution is committed to protecting your personally identifiable information. We will take reasonable precautions to protect this information from loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure or alteration, including, putting in place appropriate physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure such information. We use encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data (e.g., card information) using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

### Use of E-mail Addresses

In the ordinary course of our business, we will use the email address you provide us to confirm a payment transaction and/or to alert you regarding any difficulty we may experience in attempting to process your payment.  With your permission, we may also contact you via email to remind you of a scheduled or successfully completed payment.

### User Acceptance of Privacy Policy and Changes to Privacy Policy

By using our sites, you signify your assent to this privacy policy.  If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites.  If we make any substantial changes in this privacy policy (including with respect to how we use customer identifiable information) we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our Web sites thirty (30) days prior to implementing the change (to the extent commercially possible). Govolution encourages you to periodically review the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of Govolution services following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.    

request more information >
